Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - Reel-to-reel tapes, 154445
      - Amirkhanian / Novak / Rimbaud (Chopin) (PT 166), undated; 154662; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inch; 00:07:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886276)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6d0256da-c653-4c85-948f-9ff6521e5c87
      - Amirkhanian, Charles. "From CA to HC. Contains 5 tracks" (PT 33), 1970-1972; 154661; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:22:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886284)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4e881d8e-27ed-418b-bf0e-1316ae43c0c7
      - "Atelier Creation Radiophonique" (PT 17 A)(1 of 3), 1988; 154660; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 9 inches; 00:49:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507034)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3e86f7a4-7278-4ea7-9ea1-c734528417d5
      - "Atelier Creation Radiophonique" (PT 17 B)(2 of 3), 1988; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 9 inches; 00:50:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507042)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6c01ac40-e0a1-45e3-a937-3da5bd845866
      - "Atelier Creation Radiophonique" (PT 17 C)(3 of 3), 1988; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 8 inches; 00:37:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507059)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f08ad59c-3ce1-41b2-8e2c-daa424c701a4
      - Battier, Marc. "Verbes comme ceuillir" (PT 81), 1980 June; 154658; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:12:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886292)
        Creation: Festival International dei [?], Experimentaves, Bourses
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&65a05baa-434e-41fb-b75d-7efc2bf1bb5f
      - Battier, Marc. "Verbes comme ceuillir" (PT 44), 1980; 154657; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:12:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507067)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2e700cc2-fb66-4bba-b8fe-e2765d8f1d7d
      - Behaert, J. "John Schmitz is the message" (PT 114), 1972 November; 154656; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:08:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886300)
        Mills College
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ac544b18-a0e3-4b45-b786-c8e3c2f0a051
      - Bekaert. Untitled (PT 210), 1971; 154655; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 3 3/4 inches; 00:36:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. It was recorded at a very high level. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888710)
        Prospect, Karl Marx, 2nd of 4, 11-40 - 12.00; Tape 1, red, green
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b7dcf9a5-664a-4c3f-8621-98ba710390ef
      - Bosseur, Jean Yves. "Anna Livia's awake" (PT 111), undated; 154654; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:35:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886318)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e58b8fad-0316-4dda-8bb7-749e3b0bc7d4
      - Bosseur, Jean Yves. "Anna Livia's awake" (PT 185), undated; 154653; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:35:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The audio speeds up at the start of the tape. (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109889684)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d17a2ed0-de60-4fa7-b04b-2e9ccb3617f0
      - Brahms, Johannes. "Vier Gesänge für Frauenchor" (PT 86), undated; 154652; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:31:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. It ends abruptly. (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886326)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ab9ddbce-388f-4898-a2ef-2b5bde22432b
      - Burke, Herbert. "Experiment 'en progrès' with sound texts" (PT 183), 1976 August; 154651; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inch; 00:21:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886334)
        Presented in part at the 1976 Sound Poetry Festival. Speed 7 1/2, stereo. Recording time: approx. 25 minutes.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&72d46078-f16b-43b6-a9da-ce6b3e5baf41
      - Chopin / Hanson. "Doubble extension" (PT 75), undated; 154650; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:08:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886342)
        15" stereo CLIR, mono full spin
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6211f91f-1bdc-4047-8cd6-db04ee2ed53e
      - Chopin/Hanson. "Tête-a-tête" (PT 133), undated; 154649; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:03:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888728)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b9093783-ecf3-420c-8a36-aa41815f032e
      - Chopin / Wendt. "Voyage to California" (PT 48), 1983 May; 154648; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:20:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886359)
        S.J.S.U.; two-channel 15 ips, 1/2 track, NAB Eq
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fdb4ceda-0884-4dad-a4b8-85e2157c8d5d
      - Chopin, Henri. "Cher Cher/pizzicati" (PT 90), 1987; 154646; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:07:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888736)
        cher cher, 7'7", 19 cm; pizzicati, 6'08
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4246f0c7-02b0-433a-9e51-50b8e43136f1
      - Chopin, Henri. "La fuite des dels jamais fixes" (PT 91), 2003 October; 154645; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:09:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888751)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9c6eca15-dc57-4792-846a-b8b4ea8f21cb
      - Chopin, Henri. "Chocs, bouche, voix" (PT 92), 2005 May; 154644; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:11:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888777)
        audio-poeme (un seul instrument: bouche, voix & HC.); 19 cm/s, stereo, duree 11 minutes trente secondes
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b5826519-8623-4647-9b8d-d437b92173d7
      - Chopin, Henri. "7o émission / 8o émission" (PT 93), undated; 154643; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:27:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. The program was recorded at a very low level. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888769)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&db163f86-81d5-4c77-9031-049a2d374440
      - Chopin, Henri. "Reprise des raclements sur les monts partout" (PT 94), 2004 April; 154642; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:12:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888785)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bb7d7062-f9e0-4287-b48b-88ceaf3f51a4
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les flaques flics / Le glissements sur les peaux" (PT 83), 2004 Aug/Sept; 154641; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:30:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886367)
        Contents of the reel include the following: 5. les flaques flics 08:50, 6. les glissements sur les peaux 22:10, total environ: 32 minutes.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&55efa8e2-d64e-4687-920b-9bc2681d73c9
      - Chopin, Henri. "Reliefs sur reliefs pour une vie reelle" (PT 84), 2005 April; 154640; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inch; 00:31:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886375)
        Information included with the reel reads: stereo 19 cm/s; bouche et voix de l'auteur; recherche contre les silences imposes par toutes les religions.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bceb32c3-3dcc-41ad-a008-b7f7540ef9b7
      - Chopin, Henri. "La cavalcade échevelée" (PT 85), 1983 December; 154639; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:04:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886383)
        Tracks are listed on the back of the reel. They are as follows:
        Saintes- Phonies 1983-87
        1. "a [?]ieds", 3'08", 19 cm
        2. "en R majeur", 4' 40", 19 cm
        3. "soufflee", 3'43", 19 cm
        4. "Soubre_sautante", 5', 19 cm
        5. "de[?]echee", 2'35", 19 cm
        6. "dialogue de sourds", 5'49, 38 cm
        7. "abyssale", 3'20, 19 cm
        8. "cavalcade Echevelee", 5'
        9. "galo[p]ante", 8'40", 19 cm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fd3ac5b8-cc54-4640-896f-02b63cc26994
      - Chopin, Henri. "Faire l'amour au micros" (PT 88), 1971 December 21; 154638; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:28:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); For the first 14 minutes, a continuous hum can be heard. High frequency background noise can be heard for the last 14 minutes of the tape. (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888793)
        Note on the back cover reads: Dear Henri: This is the original. - Jan
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&74ade6fa-718f-405a-b04b-c2335aecca6f
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les chutes syncopées" (PT 87), 2004 November; 154637; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:19:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 37, Item barcode 39002109888744)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&74172e10-e6d1-4600-b169-d78d2bda2137
      - Chopin, Henri. "La vie pénètre après des siècles de radures religieuses" (PT 82), 2006 March - April; 154636; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:17:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886391)
        The back cover reads: audio offert a Matteo d'Amrosio; bouche et voix de l'auteur. It was recorded in stereo at 19 cm, single track, 17 minutes.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1479d3a6-a9b2-40fe-a417-e77b2e15a276
      - Chopin, Henri. "Symphonie du nez aux vibrisses" (PT 80), 2004 December - 2005 January; 154635; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:25:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886409)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5015f2e1-bc78-46f9-b4a4-1e1829fc7971
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les pirouettes vocales pour les pirouettements vocaux en 1995" (PT 78), 154634; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch, diameter 7 inches; 00:11:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886417)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d48b40f0-882e-49c0-8fc5-eb7b46f0a937
      - Chopin, Henri. "Discours des ministres" (PT 76), undated; 154633; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch, diameter 7 inches; 00:18:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886425)
        Chercher 7'05", 19 cm.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d4b7993e-5dd0-4556-8039-8dcc44415cbe
      - Chopin, Henri. "La peur - 1958-1970" (PT 74), 1971; 154632; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:20:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 42, Item barcode 39002109886433)
        Stereo, 19cm/s. or 7 1/2. Information on the reel also reads 15'53". Production: Sveriges radio.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&81dcd977-8d22-4c04-b5ee-da57b5e01b90
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre No 4" (PT 73), 2006; 154631; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:28:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887688)
        Speed 7 1/2, 30'; bande originale; piece en finale pour le theatre en oratorio du meme nom, voix et bouches exlusives de l'auteur
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&90dfc8af-3ac8-4866-a812-6c9a0fd2514e
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre feu pour feu" (PT 72), 2005; 154630; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:19:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887696)
        Bob Cobbing E Colony; 7 1/2 ips., 6 mins, performers Bob Cobbing and Peter Finch (jewr harp) made in Cardiff University studio, 1973; pour Marie-Cecile Miessner; Duree: 19 minutes 20, bouche et voix de l'auteur; ainsi que le studio, realise avec 2 magnetos; stereo, 19 cm
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a80e6bef-769f-4e85-9166-b781207cf781
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pêche de nuit" (PT 71), 1957; 154629; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:11:48 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887704)
        Bande unique. ti[?] [?]icicuse; 11'40; mono-38cm.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&916e8cf9-5704-47d7-a1bb-0499597ab656
      - Chopin, Henri. "Ex Plo(x)ions / Les souffles "agrippeurs" de la mer de Barents" (PT 70), 2003; 154628; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:24:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The end of the program was recorded at a very low level. (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887712)
        "Ex plo(x) ions", janvier 2003, 11 minutes; les souffles, avril/septembre 2003, 14 minutes; vitesse 19, sereo.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e1aad953-5766-4a13-b137-fcf5821428f5
      - Chopin, Henri. " Bouche souffles et voix" (PT 69), 2005 February; 154627; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:25:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887720)
        19 cm/s stereo voix de l'auteur exclusivement montage du meme, studio HC, 24 minutes environ
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7529209d-f6b2-4389-aa83-c915dc264366
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le temps aujourd'hui" (PT 68), 1976 December 17; 154626; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:07:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887738)
        7'52", 38 cm/s; [milt] + shadow
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&915b13c4-8e18-4d42-b3b9-d0b8228d6e3e
      - Chopin, Henri. "Staccati en glissandos" (PT 1), 1991; 154625; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 9 1/2 inches; 00:26:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507224)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&cfb500bb-9923-4f28-a005-a5a8b7c93b30
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le riches heures de l'alphabet" (PT 2), 1993 January 10; 154624; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:24:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507232)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b44e2216-c0c9-46b0-a062-2253383b8175
      - Chopin, Henri. " La peur" (PT 3), 1958; 154623; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 9 1/2 inches; This audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507240)
      - Chopin, Henri. " La frise majeure des levres" (PT 4), 2003; 154622; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:35:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507257)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&77b76d01-5614-4c7c-8102-164d0f9736b0
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le corpsbis" (PT 5), undated; 154621; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:46:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507190)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3855118b-683f-4066-b9be-deefe7632970
      - Chopin, Henri. "La danse des Tonneaux roulants et brisés" (PT 6), 2003 September; 154620; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:51:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507216)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&51fe4b26-d50a-4920-bc48-2d02044a4f33
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fresque de l'impalpable voix" (PT 7), 1991 December 22; 154619; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:15:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507208)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8bb1765c-1912-44b5-82f7-ff9f48850611
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamisme integral" (PT 9), undated; 154618; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 inches; 00:21:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104507265)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e37018ae-c273-46d8-b6ff-ed78c2541731
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre" (PT 10), 1956; 154617; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:33:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program sounds distorted at times. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104506994)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f9aa64b1-474a-4c00-a04a-c3dd2e105580
      - Chopin, Henri. "7 audio-poèmes de janvier à octobre 2003" (PT 11), 154616; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 00:43:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507000)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1248c830-8fb9-4ff3-9571-ff5f98ec3418
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les tubes assassins de Londres..." (PT 12), undated; 154615; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches; 01:23:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); All four tracks of the audiotape reel are meant to be played back simultaneously. Fluctuations in the speed can be heard throughout the program. (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507018)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8134acf2-1a68-4a54-92c2-84b0dcb634da
      - Chopin, Henri. " Indicatif 1 / La fusée interplanétaire..." (PT 13), 1962-1972; 154614; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:17:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 49, Item barcode 39002104507026)
        audiopoèmes, le dernier avec Denis Chopin
        Listed Contents
        "Indicatif 1", 1'
        "La fusée interplanétaire" (annonce de Jean Ratcliffe), 2' 16"
        "L' énergie du sommeil", 5'
        "Le ventre du Bertini", 3' 30"
        "La chanson du parlement eruopéan", 2'
        "Beginning" (poème création de Denis Chopin, effets électroniques H. Chopin), 3' 10"
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&449e664b-6c83-4760-8bda-50f1d419de8e
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le fond de la gorge" (PT 16), undated; 154613; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 6 inches; 00:09:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507075)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&53fa2ca3-5bfb-4cde-8fa4-9be6f1a13030
      - Chopin, Henri. "Les Chuintanes respirent" (PT 19), 1979; 154611; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:19:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104507083)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2e1045ba-5e04-4ce9-a24f-82604a65b631
      - Barrière, Françoise. "Le chant des Auriguaciens" (PT 15), 1976 June 23; 154659; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 inches; 00:25:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506234)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&360dfe09-97c8-4e49-ab6a-29fce69c7fef
      - Chopin, Henri. "OU No 30-31" (PT 18), undated; 154612; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 inches; 00:22:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506242)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c311bd02-7980-4cbd-9541-e101bdf5ac21
      - Chopin, Henri. "Vivre pour vivre no 2" (PT 20), undated; 154610; 1 Audiotape Reels; 00:36:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506259)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8e589164-9c8a-41fc-9fc0-5105e382d4b7
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamisme integral" (PT 21), undated; 154609; 1 Audiotape Reels; 00:21:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506267)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7cc7e5e9-2453-44c1-b36a-192303facda4
      - Chopin, Henri. "Staccati en glissandos" (PT 22), undated; 154608; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 1/2 inches (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506275)
        Empty, open reel. No files were digitized.
      - Chopin, Henri. "4o Staccati en Glissandos" (PT 23), undated; 154607; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 9 1/2 inches; 00:27:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506291)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f38b2df4-00cb-4b3a-a202-95c61e2e6093
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dynamique integral / French lesson" (PT 24), undated; 154606; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 10 inches; 00:20:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506309)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c171defd-9792-40a3-bf8f-b10c50bbb7bd
      - Chopin, Henri. "Plurality 1.1.1.1." (PT 25), undated; 154605; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:09:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 50, Item barcode 39002104506283)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d1c08a29-6717-4c5b-9eed-fa730be8f63d
      - Chopin, Henri. "Espace et gestes / Pêche d enuit / Sol Air" (PT 30), 1957-1961; 154602; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:47:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887746)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&62d0c4e5-ef70-4aa1-982a-c2e98524fd12
      - Chopin, Henri. "Fond de la Gorge / Civilisation de papier" (PT 32), 1974-1975; 154601; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:20:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887753)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fb10bfd8-c58c-4ac9-b0d1-07d70f787811
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le palais enchanté des années 80" (PT 36), 1980 March-1982 April; 154600; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:10:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887761)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8df5c26a-7970-46f6-bde7-278d59cf6849
      - Chopin, Henri. "La peur" (PT 38), undated; 154599; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:35:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887779)
        ces deux la a producie ensemble en mono
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&30e82f95-9e04-4d43-8ce8-1e0ca5adec70
      - Chopin, Henri. "Déplacements hors tout / Les respirations festoyantes" (PT 39), 2003 January-March; 154598; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 7 inches; 00:26:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887787)
        "Deplacements hors tout", 18 minutes 30; "les respirations festoyantes", 8 minutes 07; 19 cm, stereo
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a1e4b2f3-f9bb-4541-99c8-a9d242f99da7
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le rire est debout / (Among) II, Johnson" (PT 41), undated; 154597; 1 Audiotape Reels 1/4 inch; diameter 5 inches; 00:13:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 43, Item barcode 39002109887795)